

www.felchan.cf

+65 8381 7305

a 2 Whampoa East, Eight Riversuites #18-02, S338517

feliciachandra@outlook.com

FELICIA CHANDRA

Personal Information

Nationality : Indonesia

Date of Birth : November 2nd, 1997 : Indonesian, English, Languages

Chinese (simplified - beginner proficiency)

Summary

A fresh Master graduate with strong passion in marketing management. A perfectionist in my passionate area and an innovative individual. I'd like to perceive myself as a person with high sense of responsibility who's creative in the area of ideas and problem solving and always ready to learn new things every day. I am highly adaptive to changes and I work extra mile to ensure that expectations are exceeded. Through internship experiences and actively involved myself in various extracurricular activities and voluntary work, I am a strong team player with proven qualifications in event planning, marketing, and organization management.

Employment History

Apr 2015 – Jul 2015 Surabaya, Indonesia

Key Sales Manager at Kakita Jaya

- Manage a small team of 5 people to work side by side in attaining successful sales.
- Generate financial statements including balance sheet.
- Provide analysis and performance reports for superior.
- Oversee the newly acquired accountancy program by testing and ensure successful implementation.
- foster relationship with suppliers and customers via e-mails and phone calls.
- Provide training to new employees.

Aug 2015 – Oct 2015 Surabaya, Indonesia

Sales Executive at Ray White Property Consultant

- Manage property listing and lists of customers.
- Ensure cohesiveness between property agents team.
- Provide analysis and performance reports for superior.
- Meeting with customers and conduct presentation regarding the listing details and benefits.
- Foster relationship with suppliers and customers via e-mails and phone calls.

Education

Mar 2018 – Feb 2019

Master of Business Administration, James Cook University Singapore

• Graduation in February 2019.

Aug 2016 - Jan 2018

Bachelor of Commerce with a major in Finance, Wollongong University, Australia

Graduated with Distinction Award. GPA 5.3 out of 7.0

Diploma in Business Administration, PSB Academy Singapore

Oct 2015 – Jul 2016

Graduated with 4.0 out of 4.0 GPA.

Extracurricular & Volunteer Activities

• President of JCUS Music Club (Nov'18 – Feb'19)

- o Handled administrative responsibilities, developed and managed budget schemes
- Assigned tasks to the executive committees and monitor progress
- o Organized events (e.g. welcoming party, bonding activity) and student performances
- o Ensured cohesiveness among committees and club members
- O Report club's progress regularly to the school's staff

Publicity Manager of JCUS Music Club (Mar'18 – Nov'18)

- o Marketed events on the club's social media account
- o Designed posters and invitations for club's events
- o Documented club's activities and published on social media
- Managed and designed the club social media accounts in terms of attractiveness for maximum utilization and reaching out members

• Worship Leader of Gloria Christian High School (Jun'09 – Apr'15)

- o Managed song lists for the worship session and assigned singers and musicians.
- o Scheduled and managed practice a week before the session
- o Organized line up during the worship session
- o Acted as the speaker during the worship session

Skills

- Marketing Management
- Internet Marketing
- Corporate Finance
- Accounting
- Data Analysis
- Graphic Design (Adobe Photoshop)
- Logo Design
- Public Speaking